Laugh and eat your way to the top! It's the foodie championship!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Here we go.
Snow crab, spider crab, horsehair crab, crab masaa.
Wow!
I laughed, even a little bit.
You're so pretty.
Yum!
Delicious!
It's a little stuffed with meat.
Crab ice cream.
Oh!
Beautiful!
Delicious!
I wish I could eat totoyaki.
I'd love to have some for sunbaisse!
Osaka Osho!
Crunchy cheese dumplings.
Welcome home!
me me
me me me
If it's a word, I don't need it anymore
ana, the destiny I dreamed of
Then I forgot who's going to make me laugh again
I want to go!
I can't think of anything.
warum
Pair!Pair!
Oh, two.
Two.
I'd like to decide on a pair.
I just don't know if I can do it alone.
Better than one.
What happens if we all get out of here?
I thought you were moe.
Oh, no!
This is getting dangerous.
Let's do it again.
I can't think of anything.
Ayaan.
I thought it was good.
I thought for sure you'd bring it back.
I'll think of something.
How many people should I make laugh?
Let's make two more people laugh.
I can do it.
Let's make each one of them laugh.
It'll work.
How's that? We'll figure it out together.
That's a peeler.
It's a peeler.
We wish we could have thought of that.
Oh, my God.
I'm so hungry.
After something sweet, you always want something salty.
If we don't eat soon, we might collapse.
He's going to be in a bad mood.I'm in a bad mood.
Oh, oh, you're getting on my nerves, you're getting on my nerves, you're getting on my nerves, you're getting on my nerves.
Heart
Heart.
What are you going to do?
Southern Break and Bass, Octavus!
Dakodako dakodako!
Please let me change! I really don't want to!
I really hate it!
But you two know what you're doing!
You're so cool! Really!
It's with me! Definitely!
I wanna go home! I really want to go home!
Sabo sabo project bus, octabus!
Octopus, octopus, octopus!
I'm full!
I'll say it again!
I'm not hungry!
I'm done!
Thanks to Ilan Moeka, I got takoyaki!
Thank you!
Bon appétit!
What's going on?
They're gagging!
Bon appétit!
You didn't help me with anything!
Really!
It was nice during the day!
I'm glad you pulled the Octavus!
You two were in such trouble. Two people. I was having such a hard time.
You didn't help me!
I'm going to pull Octavus away!
You want some?
Are you okay?
I can see it if you rewind it!
Bon appétit!
I don't think I've ever had salty food before!
Looks delicious!
Is that you and Nekoji?
Are you two doing that?
Isn't it hot?
Hot!
Yummy?
Looks good.
I think I'll just stick with the salt.
How's it taste?
Oh, my God, I've got cat food.
I'm sure I'll burn myself.
Oh, my God, it's dripping.
Bon appétit!
Red, red, red! So soft!
I'll eat first.
I'll have the iran too!
Salty
Mmm!
It's going down, it's going down, it's going down.
Not salty takoyaki?
Can I eat it? Is it too noisy? It's so good!
It's so good! It's so good!The inside is tender and very tasty!
It's better when it's soft and tender inside
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry for brass.
There's something sweet around here.
I wonder if it's that one.
Oh!
It's so spicy.
Wait.
But it's exciting and strong, right?
Right?
Gentlemen.
Hey, guys.
I just ate something salty.
Next.
How about strawberry sweets?
Bon appétit!
Phew...
I found a good one.
And it smells so good with strawberries!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
Now let's decide who will do the gag first.
Let's start!
Who?
I'm on it.
I can't stand it.
I want to eat it.I want to eat already.
Ah! It's flowers!
I'm alone.
Alone.
How many people can I make laugh?
You may be served.
It's this way.
All right! You're served!
Start! We're served!
Go, go, go!
Aah!
Three!
But we were so close to being happy.
I was happy.
Goodbye.
Hang in there.
I did my best.
I'm sorry, guys.
I'm sorry.
What? I said I was sorry,
I said I was sorry, and he said we'd figure it out together.
There were a lot of clothes,
I think I'll go with the table clothes.
But the ice cream looks even better.
Ice cream is good too.
Ayanan
I'm going to go.
I'll do my best.
Well then, Aya, I look forward to working with you.
StrawberinoStroberino
1, 5 Investment
Ayanan
yay yay yay!
That's great, great, great, great.
Why is it more fun to think about it in those 3 seconds?
That was so much fun.
That was good.
That was amazing.
I'm so embarrassed.
Strawberry Tosie is funny.
It's funny. It's funny. It's funny.
That's great.
I can eat all of them.
Thank you.
That was fun.
Strawberry Torchy.
I'm sorry, they're melting. I got them first.
I had ice cream.
Yuzu went for strawberry ice cream.
Una went for green tea strawberry daifuku
I had Daifuku with strawberry whip
Seino
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Ice cream.
I love ramen and ice cream more than anything else in the world,
What a cute ice cream!
There are strawberries on the top.There are strawberries on the top.
Thanks to the flowers. Really.
It was indeed an investment in strawberries.
Delicious.
Aren't they pretty?
They are delicious.
I think I'll have that last one.
What was the best theme of the day?
Embarrassment.
I know, I know.
Can I do it right?
Let's do it the same way I do it.
I understand.
Ready!
Strawberry toasting!
Bye-bye!